本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译： 艾丝凡  鸟  V羊羊  土豆  索普  猫中之王
时间轴:  深夏桃子  坌Φ暮ｋ  子衿 后期制作:  、青衣
■
校对: 芒果 郁金香 士也瓜  总监: 爱吃屎的鱼
《复仇》前情提要
Previously on Revenge.
艾米莉不是你的挚友  阿曼达
Emily's not your friend, Amanda.
需要更多的证明吗
You need more proof?
我打给你律师了
I called your lawyer
我让她送来了离婚文书
I had her send over a messenger with the divorce papers.
是时候了结这一切了
It's time to end this.
你家人一刻不停地来电话
Your family has been calling nonstop.
你最终还是得面对他们的
You gotta face 'em eventually.
杰克・波特
羟考酮止痛片  遵医嘱服用
拿好箱子
Take the box.
将你父亲的秘密带离此处  掩埋起来
Bury your father's secrets away from here.
和我去巴黎吧
Come to Paris with me.
我做不到
I can't.
你好啊  丹尼
Hello, Danny.
不  不要  不要  阿曼达
No! No, no, no! Amanda!
-我的天  -我没有
- My god.  - I-I didn't.
快走  我的卡车就停在路边
Go. My truck's up the road.
钥匙在里面
The keys are inside.
喂
Hey!
妈妈
Mom!
是泰勒
It's tyler.
妈妈
Mom?
我
I...
什么也别说
Don't say a word.
我父亲的含冤入狱教会我
My father's false imprisonment taught me that
危机时如何迅速辨别谁是真朋友
in a crisis you quickly find out who your real friends are.
身处悲剧与丑闻漩涡时  似乎
Tragedy and scandal, it seems,
我们才能搞清何为心中至重
have a unique way of clarifying people's priorities.
我们听到海岸沙丘那边
We heard a cell phone ring
有一阵手机铃声
up by the sand dune.
我看到一个穿深色帽衫的人
I saw someone in a dark hoodie
藏在锯齿草丛后
hiding behind the saw grass.
我不知道  可能穿了件帽衫
I don't know. It could've been a hoodie.
也可能是别的  比如是派对的嘉宾
It could've been anything, like a guest from the party.
真说不好
It's hard to say.
泰勒不是个坏人  他病了
Tyler wasn't a bad person. He--he was sick.
那家伙让我手臂开了花
The guy went all benihana on my arm
还把我绑在椅子上
and tied me to a chair.
那家伙是个讨厌鬼
That boy was a menace.
你们这些人要是再尽职点
If you people had been doing your jobs,
就该在这个疯子拿着枪把我当人质之后
you'd have made sure the little psychopath
把他严密看押起来
stayed locked up after holding us all hostage at gunpoint.
我回家去拿丹尼尔的衣服的时候
When I went home to get Daniel clothes,
我发现我的枪不见了
I saw that my gun was missing.
我忘了关窗  泰勒肯定是
I'd left a window open. Tyler must have...
趁我们都在派对时  偷偷潜入偷了枪
Broken in and stolen it while we were at the party.
你和巴罗先生当时为什么打架
So what were you and Mr. Barrol fighting about?
我不记得我们打过架
I don't remember a fight.
你头上缝了15针
You have 15 stitches in your head.
这你怎么解释
How do you explain that?
泰勒有暴力史
Tyler had a history of violence,
他在你生日派对上 威胁过你们全家
he threatened your whole family at your birthday party.
瞧  我理解
Look, I can understand
你觉得当时命悬一线
if you felt like your life was in danger...
所以你射杀了他  是不是
You shot him, didn't you?
什么也别说
Don't say a word.
我不记得了
I don't remember.
格雷森先生  夫人
Mr. and Mrs. Grayson,
你们在汉普顿这几个月可真多彩啊
you've had a very busy few months here in the Hamptons.
你会对他提起诉讼吗
Are you charging him?
目前不会
Not yet,
如果你们想趁着劳动节的返城流
but if you're planning on joining
逃入城里的话
the Labor Day exodus to the city,
趁早打消此念
don't.
我们现在带他回家
Well, then we're going to be taking him home.
你们可能忘了  他头部受到重创
In case it's lost upon you, he has severe head injury.
他同样浑身浴血  很可能是受害者的血
He's also covered in blood, presumably the victim's,
而受害者明显是被从他未婚妻手枪中
who was apparently killed by bullets
射出的子弹所杀
fired from his fiancee's gun.
不  我们仍有许多问题要问
No, we still have a lot of questions.
在他的律师到来前  不会回答你的问题
Yeah, which won't be answered until his lawyer is present.
或者你希望我现在叫律师来
Or do you want me to call him right now
告诉他我儿子的权利正在受到侵害吗
and just let him know that my son's rights are being violated?
格雷森先生  跟我走
Mr. Grayson, come with me.
来吧  咱们回家
Come on. Let's go home.
外面有车等着
We have a car waiting for you.
我和艾米莉走
I'm gonna go with Emily,
但我得先和我妈谈谈
but I need to speak to my mother first...
单独谈谈
Alone.
听你的
Whatever you need.
干得好  跑回家制造证据
Smart move, running back to the house to create a cover
解释为何泰勒拿着你的枪
for how Tyler got your gun.
这说不定无关紧要
It might not even matter.
泰勒说不定已将真相告诉丹尼尔了
Tyler could've told Daniel everything.
泰勒的话不可靠
Tyler's not exactly a reliable source,
而且  丹尼尔爱你
and... Daniel loves you.
除非这种爱意已变
Unless that's changed.
在派对上我们吵了一架
We had an argument at the party.
我也不知道我们身处何处
I'm not sure where we stand.
你现在身处警局
Well, you're standing in a police station,
而且我认为更重要的是
and I would say the more pressing issue
你父亲的无尽之盒的下落
is the whereabouts of your father's infinity box.
绝对安全
It's safe and sound.
准备走了吗
You ready to go?
是的
Yeah.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
你刚才和你妈妈说了什么
What were you talking to your mother about?
我们在派对上有过争执
We had words at the party.
我只想
I just...
我只想消除一下误解
I just wanted to clear the air.
这很好啊  你现在需要
That's good. You're gonna need...
能找到的所有支持
As much support as you can get right now.
丹尼尔  你和泰勒在海滩上到底发生了什么
Daniel, what happened on the beach with you and Tyler?
汤姆・金斯莱
米歇尔・班克斯
弗兰克・史蒂芬
梅森・特德韦尔
这什么啊
What's this?
不如我们打给你未婚妻  问问她
Why don't we call your fiancee and ask her?
不管怎么说
I did, after all,
这是我在她客厅的地板里找到的
find it underneath her living room floorboards.
我不记得了
I don't remember.
我让厨师准备了早饭
I had the cook set up some breakfast
以防你们饿了
in case you're hungry.
我也一直在网上跟踪媒体
I've also been tracking the media coverage
对丹尼尔的相关报道
of Daniel online.
等等  等一下  怎么
Wait a second. Wait. How, uh...
谁通知的媒体
Who alerted the media?
网上有一张丹尼尔穿着
Well, there's a picture online of Daniel
染血燕尾服的照片
in his bloody tux.
肯定是派对上的某人偷拍的
Someone from the party must have snapped it.
他们可真懂得礼貌啊
Oh, well, so much for decorum.
她说的没错  网上已经传遍了
She's right. It's everywhere.
百万富豪海滩血战
"Bloody billionaire beach battle"?
警方真以为是丹尼尔杀的泰勒吗
Do the police really think Daniel killed Tyler?
当然不是
Of course not.
我父亲已经乘直升飞机飞回城里
Well, dad took the helicopter into the city.
飞机回来时  我保证载回来
When it returns, I've made sure
曼哈顿最好的
the best defense attorney in Manhattan
辩护律师
is gonna be on board.
阿什莉  你能帮我拿片阿司匹林吗
Ashley, could you please get me an aspirin?
当然可以
Of course.
我认为她的精力更应该
I think her time would be better
集中于如何把那张照片撤下来
spent trying to get that photograph taken down.
好的  我会打给诺兰・罗斯
Okay, I'll call Nolan Ross
问问我们能否借用他的技术团队
and see if we can have access to his tech team.
至于这位小姐  你得睡觉去了
And you should get to bed, young lady.
好好休息
Get some rest.
接下来的几天肯定风起云涌  极富挑战
The next few days are gonna be challenging.
我只是来拿换洗衣物的
I'm only here to pick up clothes.
我要回德克兰那里
I'm going back to Declan's.
亲爱的  我们需要你留在这里
Sweetheart, we need you to stay here.
你哥哥有大麻烦了
Your brother's in real trouble,
我们作为家人得团结起来
and we need to stay together as a family.
你妈妈说得对
Your mother's right.
我们得统一战线
We need to present a united front.
好吧
Fine.
你一旦搬回来了  我就马上回来
I'll move back in when you do.
看吧
That's what I thought.
你一定累坏了
You must be exhausted.
山姆
Hey, Sammy.
你该带它去遛一圈
You should take him for a walk.
我会的
I will.
先换件衣服
Just gonna change first.
你去哪了
Where you been?
天呐  德克
Oh, jeez. Dec.
你吓死我了
You scared the hell outta me.
你在这里干什么
What are you doing in here?
我在想你发生什么事了
I've been wondering what happened to you.
我以为你起航去海地了
I thought you sailed off to Haiti.
我的引擎坏了
My engine crapped out.
一小时前我看到阿曼达号还在泊位时
I figured that when I saw the "Amanda" in her slip
就猜到了
an hour ago.
那你这段时间都上哪去了
So where you been all this time?
凌晨五点了  伙计
It's 5:00 in the morning, man.
你怎么还不睡
Why aren't you sleeping?
今晚太离奇了
Well, it's been a crazy night.
泰勒被杀了
Tyler was murdered.
泰勒
Tyler?
我和夏洛特发现他的
Me and Charlotte found him.
丹尼尔浑身是血地从一个沙丘后突然出现
And Daniel pops up from a dune, covered in blood.
太  太不可思议了
That's-- that's insane.
-你  你没事吧  -没事
- Are-- are you okay? - Fine.
不过夏洛特已经筋疲力尽了
Charlotte's a wreck, though.
她告诉警察她在沙滩上看到一个穿着
She told the cops that she saw some guy in a hoodie
连帽衫的人在泰勒的尸体旁边
on the beach by Tyler's body.
那你呢
What about you?
我离得太远了
I was too far away.
没看清他的脸
I didn't get a good look at his face.
我去睡了
I'm gonna crash.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
寻找答案
Looking for answers.
这是什么
What is this?
不知道  肯定是上一任屋主的
I don't know. It must belong to the previous owner.
你怎么
How did you--
泰勒告诉我说你一直在玩弄我
Tyler told me you've been playing me,
还说你在地板下面藏有秘密
that you had secrets hidden underneath the floorboards.
丹尼尔
Daniel,
泰勒疯了
Tyler was crazy.
他是个骗子
He was a liar.
他用枪指着我们
He held us at gunpoint.
你说得对  我很抱歉
You're right. I'm sorry.
不
No.
你不必道歉
You don't need to apologize.
你受伤了  是心理创伤
You're injured, you're traumatized.
我爱你  丹尼尔
I love you, Daniel.
无论发生什么事我都会陪着你
I'm gonna be by your side no matter what.
来吧  你需要好好睡一觉
Come on. You need to get some sleep.
《复仇》  第一季第十六集
眼下
As of now,
丹尼尔还未受到任何指控
Daniel hasn't been charged with anything.
我们只知道
All we know is,
泰勒・巴罗似乎是中枪而死
Tyler Barrol appears to have been shot to death
而丹尼尔神志不清  浑身是血
and Daniel was found unconscious at the scene
出现在了现场
with some blood on him.
大家都在等待法医的验尸报告
Everyone's waiting on the coroner's report
以及你的指纹比对结果
as well as the results from your fingerprint
和枪击残留物测试结果
and gunshot residue test.
直到这些结果出来之前
Until those come back,
我们都不知道要辩护的是什么罪名
we won't know what we're up against.
布鲁克斯先生
Mr. Brooks,
我想告诉你我们不胜感激
I want to tell you how grateful we are
你同意做丹尼尔的辩护律师
that you've agreed to represent Daniel
我和我丈夫可以协助你
and that you can count on my husband and I
并肩作战
to work as a team.
你丈夫呢
Where is your husband?
布鲁克斯先生很宽容  没有质疑你的缺席
Mr. Brooks was kind enough not to question your absence,
但我可没这么好说话
but I am not feeling so indulgent.
我都没睡过觉  我很累
I haven't slept. I'm tired.
我也不想让我们的往事笼罩着那间房
And I didn't want our history clouding the room.
197次航班的
246 fatalities
爆炸造成了246起死亡
in the bombing of Flight 197.
加上许多下落不明的人
The final death toll will likely surge
最终的死亡人数可能会更多
to include the many unaccounted for...
康拉德  你还好吗
Conrad, are you all right?
在现场
On the ground.
一组国内的暴力激进分子
A homegrown group of violent radicals...
怎么了
What is it?
声称自己是反美倡议联盟
Calling themselves the Americon Initiative...
我犯了一个很严重很严重的错
I've made a terrible, terrible mistake.
总统昨晚受这条消息的启迪
The president, awakened last night to news...
你知道那架坠毁的飞机  197次航班吗
Uh, you know the plane that went down, Flight 197?
我要为此负责的
I'm responsible.
你到底在说什么
What on earth are you talking about?
那个声称要为爆炸案负责的组织
That group that claimed responsibility for the bombing,
我在给他们洗黑钱
I was laundering money for them.
康拉德
Conrad.
案件调查会联系到公司
The investigation's gonna tie back to the company.
我下半辈子都要蹲监狱了
I'm gonna go to prison for the rest of my life,
这还是运气好的情况
if I'm lucky.
他们会冻结我们所有的资产
They're gonna freeze all of our assets,
而你就要在别人耻笑的眼光下
and you're gonna have to raise Daniel alone
独自一人抚养丹尼尔长大了
under a cloud of disgrace.
我们之前过的日子  维多利亚
Life as we know it, Victoria,
已经结束了
is over.
无论我们多想逃离过去
No matter how much we try to escape our past,
似乎命中注定历史会重演
we seem destined to repeat it.
不管你喜不喜欢  我们要共同面对
Like it or not, we are in this together,
再一次的
again.
很高兴见到你  老朋友
Good to see you, old timer.
好孩子
Good boy.
杰克
Jack.
你现在不是该在
Shouldn't you be on a boat
去海地的船上吗
halfway to Haiti right now?
我的引擎不给力
Yeah, well, my engine had other ideas.
你还好吗
You okay?
我没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
我担心的是丹尼尔
It's Daniel I'm worried about.
警察在对他严加审问
The police were questioning him pretty hard.
他们还有其他嫌疑人吗
Do they have any other suspects?
不知道  他们什么都不肯告诉我们
I don't know. They're not really keeping us in the loop.
德克兰怎么样
How's Declan?
找到泰勒的尸体一定是段糟糕的经历
Finding Tyler's body must have been pretty awful.
他  他看着挺冷静的  但是
Yeah, he's, uh, he's playing it cool, but...
我不相信
I'm not buying it.
阿曼达不会碰巧找过你吧
You haven't heard from Amanda, by any chance, have you?
没有
No.
还是没联系上她吗
Still no luck getting ahold of her?
没有  她的手机打不通
No, her phone's disconnected.
不管怎样  多谢你
Anyway, thank you
照顾山姆了
for looking after Sammy.
乐意效劳
Anytime.
我要看一下杰克船上发生什么事了
I need to see what happened on Jack's boat.
他没有离开镇子
He never left town.
什么  他现在应该都到外滩群岛附近了
What? He should be down around the Outer Banks by now.
可他出现在了我家门廊上
Try my back porch.
不可能  我发誓他离开港口了
No, I swear, he left the harbor.
我看到的  或者说
I saw him or...
至少小鲸鱼看见了
at least, uh, Shamu did.
看到没  我跟你说的没错吧
See? What did I tell you?
杰克
Jack!
杰克  等等
Jack, wait!
阿曼达
Amanda?
你怎么来这了
What are you doing here?
我的错  亲爱的
Mea culpa, babe.
杰克说船的引擎出了问题
Jack said he had engine trouble
而他最后一次见阿曼达是在上星期
and the last time he saw Amanda was last week.
他为什么要对我撒谎
Why would he lie to me?
有可能是为了隐瞒阿曼达惹的什么祸
Probably because he's covering up another one of her messes.
跟他谈谈  看能否问出阿曼达为何回来
Talk to him. See if you can find out why Amanda came back.
还有她现在的藏身何处  对吗
And where she's been hiding, right?
这一点尤其要弄清楚
Especially that.
夏洛特  你在干吗呢
Hey, Charlotte, what are you doing?
我昨晚几乎没怎么睡
I barely slept last night.
头疼得要命
My head is pounding.
你不知道这几天我过的是什么日子
You've no idea what these past few days have been like for me,
发现大卫・克拉克是我生亲
finding out David Clarke is my father,
而现在丹尼尔又被卷入
and now Daniel getting wrapped up
泰勒的命案调查之中
in Tyler's murder investigation,
我还在后怕  我们当时很有可能
knowing how close we probably came
也会死在那个可怕的
to getting killed, too...
穿连帽衫的家伙手里
by that creepy guy in the hoodie.
或许你应该再去咨询那位心理医生
Uh, well, maybe you should call that shrink again.
你上次说她帮了很大的忙
You said she really helped last time.
跟人倾诉并不那么有效
Talking's overrated.
难道嗑药就有效吗
And taking pills isn't?
你昨晚嗑药了是吗
Were you high last night?
别这样  夏洛特
Come on, Charlotte.
你现在更应该保持冷静
You're supposed to be the smart one here.
而你应该站在我这边
And you're supposed to be on my side.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
我这周末已经被质问得够多了
I've had enough interrogation for one weekend.
汉普顿花花公子谋杀案登上名人法庭
我们真该去巴黎的
We should've gone to Paris.
我知道
I know.
真抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我们是汉普顿警局的
Hamptons Police Department.
请稍等
Just a minute.
他们会刁难我的吧
They're gonna fry me, aren't they?
不  不会的
No. No.
不  我不会允许他们那么做的  好吗
No, I'm not gonna let that happen, okay?
索恩女士  我们是汉普顿警局的
Ms. Thorne, Hamptons Police Department.
好吗
Okay?
索恩女士  我们受命逮捕丹尼尔
Ms. Thorne, we have a warrant for Daniel's arrest.
请现在就开门
Open the door now.
就是他
That's him.
丹尼尔・格雷森
Daniel Grayson,
现以谋杀泰勒・巴罗的嫌疑逮捕你
you're under arrest for the murder of Tyler Barrol.
-你不必...  -退后
- You don't have to-- - Stay back.
丹尼尔  你们别碰我儿子
Daniel. Take your hands off my son!
艾米莉的枪上有丹尼尔的指纹
Daniel's fingerprints were found on Emily's gun.
他以前拿过那把枪很多次
He handled that gun a dozen times.
他的手上也检测出了开枪火药残留
His hands were tested positive for gunshot residue.
他燕尾服上溅到的血
The blood splatter on his tuxedo
和泰勒的血型一致
was the same type as Tyler's.
鉴于现在的政治局势
In a political climate like this,
检察官认定这是一级谋杀案
the D.A. goes first-degree murder.
好吧  现在你该告诉我们
All right, it's time you told us
那天海滩上发生的一切了  孩子
everything that happened on that beach, son.
没关系
It's okay.
说吧
Do it.
泰勒当时满口胡言  挥舞着那把枪
Tyler was talking crazy, waving the gun around.
我们扭打起来  我设法抢到了枪
We had a struggle, and I managed to get ahold of it.
然后他就冲我扑了过来
And then he charged at me.
接着说
Keep going.
于是我就开枪了
So I fired.
连发三枪吗
Three times?
就一枪  然后我昏过去了
Once, then I blacked out.
再然后  我就只记得妈妈在叫我
Next thing I remember was my mother calling my name.
泰勒身中三弹
Tyler was shot three times.
胸口一处  背后两处
Once in the chest, twice the back.
我没有对泰勒背后开枪
I didn't shoot Tyler in the back.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
我记得你说你昏过去了
I thought you said you blacked out.
你和泰勒扭打时
When you and Tyler struggled...
他打了你哪里
where did he hit you?
就在这  在头的侧面
Right here, on the side of the head.
你脑后有一处血肿
There's a hematoma on the back of your head.
如果你们是面对面打  很难伤到那里
That's a hard spot to reach if you're fighting face-to-face.
我们由此可以推断
We can use it to float the theory
海滩上另有人在
there was a third person on the beach
此人打昏你之后
that knocked you out,
构陷了你
set you up.
你们很有钱  招谁记恨了没有
You're rich. Who hates you--
比如心存不满的投资者或敌对的竞争对手
Disgruntled investors, hostile competitors?
阿曼达・克拉克
Amanda Clarke.
好极了
Ah. Great.
我们上哪能找到她
Where can we find her?
格雷森夫人  格雷森夫人
Mrs. Grayson. Mrs. Grayson.
你儿子将面临牢狱之灾
How does it feel to have your son
对此你有何感想
facing life in prison?
格雷森先生  此事对格雷森国际的股票
Mr. Grayson, what affect will a murder trial
-会造成什么影响  -格雷森夫人
- have on Grayson Global stock? - Mrs. Grayson.
格雷森家族对此不予置评
The Grayson family have no comment...
你认为行凶的是你儿子吗
Do you think your son did it?
他们只想声明  丹尼尔是无辜的
except to say that Daniel is innocent of the charges
他们坚信司法会还他一个公道
and they're sure that justice will be served.
阿曼达
Amanda?
维多利亚
Victoria.
进来吧
Come on in.
你和丹尼尔决定结婚的时候
Well, when you and Daniel decided to get married,
恐怕没想到你们订婚时
you probably never would've dreamed that your engagement
会牵扯到一桩命案的调查
would have included a... murder investigation.
没人想得到
I don't think anyone could imagine
会有这么可怕的事发生
something so horrible.
鉴于现状
Well, under the circumstances,
如果你想要重新考虑你们未来的关系
I would understand if you were reevaluating
我是能够理解的
the future of your relationship.
所以
So...
这是我送你们的订婚礼物
this is my engagement present to the two of you.
你想让我现在就打开吗
You want me to open it now?
不
No.
我想让你原封不动地收着它
I want you to hold on to it.
我想确认无论丹尼尔未来的路多么艰难
And I need to know that you'll stand by Daniel's side
你都会在他身边予以支持
no matter how rough the road gets.
如果你抛弃了他
If you abandon him,
公众舆论会对他的清白产生怀疑
it'll send a very public message about his innocence.
实话说  我从没想过要离开他
Honestly, that never even crossed my mind.
艾米莉
Emily.
维多利亚
Victoria.
我们都还在警察局的时候
Why did you come back to this house
你为何独自回这座房子来
when we were all at the police station?
我知道他们会没收丹尼尔身上那套衣服
I knew that they would take Daniel's suit.
我想确保他们没收了之后
I wanted to make sure that he had a change of clothing
丹尼尔有衣服换
for when they did.
想得真周到
Well, that was quick thinking.
或许你在少管所的经历
Maybe your time in the juvenile detention facility
在丹尼尔上庭受审时会有所帮助
will end up being an asset in Daniel's court case.
我有一个疑问  不知道还能去问谁
I got a problem and I don't know where else to go.
你怎么找到这儿的
Uh, oh, welcome to the Cone of Silence.
你知道这是什么吗
You know what this is?
一张五百万美金的电汇凭证
A... wire receipt for $5 million.
有人从南安普顿信托公司
Someone sent it from the Southampton Trust
汇款到蒙特利尔外的一个小银行
to a small bank outside of Montreal.
我给银行打过电话
I called the bank, but I couldn't get 'em
但他们没向我透露汇款人的任何信息
to give me any information on who it came from.
是你汇的吗
Was it you?
不是
No.
那一定是格雷森家的人干的
Then it must have been the Graysons.
我觉得这一定和海滩上发生的事有关
I think this had something to do with what happened on the beach.
是吗  你真想要卷入谋杀案的调查中吗
Oh, really, 'cause you want to get wrapped up in a murder investigation?
我已经深陷其中了
I already am.
这凭证是在阿曼达的外套里发现的
The receipt was in Amanda's jacket.
我记得你说过她已经离开了
I thought you said she left.
我准备出发的那天晚上  她突然出现了
She showed up the other night as I was heading out.
我们都准备好去海地了  她却忽然走了
We were all set to go to Haiti, and she took off.
诺兰
Nolan...
诺兰  我跟踪她到了海滩
Nolan, I followed her to the beach.
我找了她好几个小时
I spent hours looking for her.
把周围都找遍了
I-I--driving around.
她就那样不见了
She was gone.
她可能直接去了加拿大
Probably straight to Canada
去取这五百万了吧
to collect the $5 million.
既然你问我的意见
You asked for my advice
那我就直说了
so I'm not gonna sugarcoat it.
把这个凭证扔了  让这件事过去吧
Throw away the receipt and let it go.
顺便
And while you're at it,
把阿曼达也忘了吧
why don't you let Amanda go, too?
我不能那么做
I can't do that.
杰克
Jack!
我是艾米莉  有事请留言
This is Emily. Leave a message.
速回电
Call me...
尽快
ASAP.
这件事得坐下好好商量
You're gonna want to sit down for this one.
你相信是丹尼尔杀了泰勒吗
Do you believe Daniel killed Tyler?
当然不信
Of course not.
网上流传的关于他的那些事
The stuff they're saying about him online,
根本就不像在说他  而是另一个截然不同的人
it's like they're talking about a completely different person.
都是一派胡言
They are.
我真希望能做点什么帮帮他
I just wish there was something I could do to help him.
当你发现大卫・克拉克干了那些万恶之事后
Is this what it was like for you when you found out
是不是也是这种感觉
David Clarke did all those hideous things?
每次看着我的时候  你都会想到他吗
Do you think about him every time you look at me?
夏洛特
Charlotte.
妈妈  我想要了解他
I want to know about him, mom,
他和你在一起的时候是什么样的人
what kind of person he was when he was with you.
感觉你我之间相隔了千万里
It feels like you're a million miles away.
要真是这样就好了
If only.
我的阿姨夏洛特在堪萨斯州有一个农场
You know, my aunt Charlotte has a farm in Kansas--
有50英亩
50 acres.
我们可以收拾好行李  今晚就走
We could pack our bags and leave tonight.
我不能把丹尼尔留给康拉德
I can't leave Daniel with Conrad.
我们可以把孩子也带上
Well, we can pack two bags, bring the kids with us.
当康拉德发现我们的事情后
Besides, when Conrad finds out about us,
我也没法待在华尔街了
I'm gonna be finished on Wall Street.
无论如何我都得走人了
I'm gonna be packing my bags regardless.
所以才不能让任何人发现我们的事情  大卫
Well, that's why no one can find out about us, David.
我经历过那种生活
I've lived that life before,
我再也不想过那种日子了
and I can't live it again.
那爱情呢
Well... what about love?
没了爱情你还能活吗
Can you live without that?
我保证总有一天我会告诉你一切
I promise to tell you everything one day,
但今天不行
but today is not the day.
你得好好想想你在海滩上看到的那个人
I need you to think hard about that person you saw on the beach.
也许会想起一些你之前没注意到的细节
You might remember things that you don't realize.
你听懂了吗
Do you understand me?
你哥哥可能就命悬于此
Your brother's life may depend on it.
我收到留言了  有什么重要的事
I got your message. What's so important?
杰克在阿曼达的外套里发现了电汇凭证
Jack found the wire transfer receipt in Amanda's jacket.
你知道阿曼达向他透露了多少吗
Did you find out how much Amanda told him?
听起来在她离开之前
It doesn't sound like she had a lot of time
没什么时间和杰克聊天
to chat before she took off.
你有没有发现
You ever notice how,
她总像嗜杀女郎版的地鼠一样
whenever you want her to leave,
每次你想她离开时
girlfriend keeps popping up
她就会突然冒出来
like the homicidal stripper version of whac-a-mole,
但每次你要找她时
but whenever you need to find her,
她就消失了
she vanishes?
还让杰克越陷越深
And manages to pull Jack even deeper into trouble.
索恩小姐
Ms. Thorne?
我等下给你回电话
I'll call you back.
布鲁克斯先生
Mr. Brooks.
很抱歉冒昧来访
I apologize for the ambush,
但我希望能和你单独谈谈
but I wanted to speak to you alone.
恕我直言
To be perfectly blunt,
我掌握丹尼尔越多的丑闻
the more dirt I have on Daniel,
我就能更从容地面对对方的攻辩
the better prepared I'll be when the fur starts flying.
原来是来找家丑的啊
Ah. Looking for skeletons.
家丑  毒瘾
Skeletons, addictions,
私情
secret relationships,
癖性
proclivities.
真是直言不讳啊
Wow. You are blunt.
你的未婚夫有可能被判谋杀罪
Your fiance's facing a murder charge.
现在可不是拐弯抹角的时候
This isn't the time for subtlety.
维多利亚坚信阿曼达・克拉克
Victoria is convinced Amanda Clarke had something to do
与海滩上发生的那件事有关系
with what happened on that beach.
你最近有见到她吗
Have you had any run-ins with her?
今年夏天我才认识她
I just met her this summer.
其实她以前在这房子里住过
She used to live in this house, actually.
她来过一次
She came by once
寻找儿时的回忆
looking for childhood memories.
你觉得她会恨格雷森家恨到
Do you believe she hates the Graysons enough
要把谋杀罪栽赃给丹尼尔吗
to frame Daniel for murder?
我觉得你得去找她
I think you'd have to find her
然后问她
And ask her.
我所知道的只是
All I know is,
她是个麻烦缠身的人
she's a very troubled girl.
我已经在调查她的行踪了
I already have my investigators on it.
谢谢配合  索恩小姐
Thank you, Ms. Thorne.
布鲁克斯先生
Mr. Brooks.
既然我们都如此坦诚
Since we're being candid...
我想有些事情应该让你知道
I think there is something you should know.
是关于丹尼尔还是阿曼达的
About Daniel or Amanda?
关于格雷森家的
About the Graysons.
我知道近几年
I understand Daniel got into a few scrapes
丹尼尔惹了一些麻烦
over the last few years.
但在他这个年纪
Like anyone his age,
年轻人总会有些鲁莽
he's had a few youthful indiscretions.
那你和康纳德是怎么处理这些鲁莽的呢
And what role did you and Conrad play in those indiscretions?
我不懂你在说什么
I'm not sure I follow you.
你们真以为我不会发现
Did you honestly believe I wouldn't find out
去年夏天  你们花钱买通法官
you paid off a judge last summer
减轻了丹尼尔酒驾和过失伤害罪的判罚吗
to downgrade daniel's D.U.I. And reckless endangerment charges?
你从哪里听说到这些的
Where on earth did you hear this?
是我告诉他的
I told him.
我以为你是站在丹尼尔这边的
I thought you were on Daniel's side.
还是说那只是个诡计
Or was that just a ruse?
就我而言  艾米莉是这里唯一一个
As far as I'm concerned, Emily is the only one here
真正关心丹尼尔利益的人
who seems to have Daniel's best interests at heart.
没有人比我更爱我的儿子
No one loves my son more than I do.
要是控方律师
What if the prosecution
拿这案子攻我不备怎么办
had blindsided me with that mid-trial?
我们处理得很谨慎
We were very discreet.
那女孩差点死掉
That girl was almost killed.
她哥拿着9寸长的铁撬往丹尼尔的车上砸
Her brother took a 9-iron to Daniel's Aston Martin.
[阿斯顿・马丁  英国豪华轿车品牌]
很多人心知肚明
Many people know exactly what you did.
每个人都想在1%的富人中
Everyone's looking for a member
找到一个能穷追猛打的人
of the 1% to smack down,
而丹尼尔正成为了他们的目标
and Daniel is tailor-made to take that fall.
除非你们准备跟我说实话
So unless you're ready to level with me,
否则我还不如去辛尼克山[美国一高级俱乐部]
I might as well be up at Shinnecock Hills
练网球好了
practicing my backswing.
当然  布鲁克斯先生
Of course, Mr. Brooks.
从现在起
From here on out, you'll have
我们将坦诚相待  绝无保留
complete and utter candor from both of us.
阿曼达・克拉克那有线索吗
Do you have any leads on Amanda Clarke?
还在查
Still working on it.
你知道她和经营偷渡者酒吧的
Did you know that she dated that young man
年轻人交往过吗
who runs the Stowaway Tavern in Montauk?
名叫杰克・波特
His name is Jack Porter.
我会去找他的
I'll pay him a visit.
但我现在更关心的
But my more immediate concern
是订婚宴的监控录像
is the security tapes from the party.
怎么了
What now?
很明显  它们被篡改了
Apparently, they were tampered with.
那晚监控录像的大部分
Kept on a 3-minute loop
都重复播着特定的三分钟
for the bulk of the evening.
那对我们有什么影响吗
And how does that impact us?
控方会使之看起来像是
The prosecution will make it look like
丹尼尔事先动了手脚
Daniel engineered it
这样没人会看见他杀死泰勒
so no one would see him kill Tyler.
你为武田聪工作多久了
How long have you been working for Takeda?
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我知道是你弄坏了订婚宴的安保摄像头
I know you disabled the security cameras at the party.
一看就是为了掩盖武田聪
It's got Takeda's stamp all over it.
要我再给你点颜色瞧瞧吗
Do I really need to kick your ass again?
他是怎么收买你的
How did he recruit you?
好吧我说
Okay.
今夏早些时候
He cozied up to me
他在投资者聚会上刻意接近我
at the investors' shindig earlier this summer.
他要我照看你
He wanted me to look out for you.
你为什么没跟我说
Why didn't you tell me?
因为他叫我保密
Because he told me not to,
而且他很令人信服
and he can be very convincing.
很抱歉  艾米
I'm sorry, Ems.
不  知道吗  是我的错
No, you know what? It's my fault.
我不该让你深陷此事
I should never have brought you so deep into this.
现在说这些
Well, it's a little late to put that genie
为时已晚了
back in the infinity box.
我们现在手上有比你的忠诚问题
Anyway, we have more pressing problems
更棘手的事要解决
than your loyalty issues.
格雷森家的人在找阿曼达
The Graysons are on a mission to find Amanda.
但找到她之前  他们肯定会先抓个
Until they do, they're gonna be looking for a fall guy
更近的替罪羊
closer to home.
杰克
Jack.
达文波特女士  格雷森家族是如何
Ms. Davenport, how are the Graysons holding up
度过这段艰难时期的
during this very difficult time?
他们深受打击
They're devastated.
丹尼尔・格雷森被捕是极其不公正的
Daniel Grayson's arrest is a terrible injustice.
我们提出的证据
The evidence will show
不仅能为丹尼尔洗脱嫌疑
that not only did Daniel not commit the crime,
还能证明当晚在海边有第三者
but that there was another person on the beach that night
他既有动机也有能力
who had both the motive and the means
杀死泰勒・巴罗  并嫁祸给丹尼尔
to murder Tyler Barrol and frame Daniel for the crime.
格雷森家族悬赏十万美金
The Grayson family are offering a $100,000 reward
奖励提供凶手线索的群众
for any information leading to the conviction of the killer.
夏洛特
Charlotte.
还好吗
Is everything okay?
从这看海滩最美了
This is the prettiest spot on the beach.
如此的平静
It's so peaceful.
是啊  我很幸运
Yeah, I really lucked out.
不敢相信  我从小就有个姐姐就住在隔壁
Hard to believe I grew up with a sister right next door
而我却浑然不知
and I never had any idea.
你觉得她早就知道真相吗
Do you think she knew the truth this whole summer?
我妈妈觉得是
My mother thinks she did.
我真的有好多问题想问她
There's just so much I want to ask her
关于她的生活  她父亲
about her life, her father...
我们的父亲
Our father.
但现在看来已经没机会了
But chances are, that won't happen now.
这就是你嗑药的原因吗
Is that why you've been taking those pills?
你知道吗
You know...
杰克和阿曼达有天来我家时
Jack and Amanda came over one day and...
告诉我这秋千是你爸亲手做的
They told me that your father built this swing.
他不可能完全是那么坏的人
He couldn't have been all bad.
杰克  有时间聊两句吗
Hey, Jack, you got a sec?
行  什么事
Yeah. What's up?
还记得我九岁那年
Do you remember when I was 9,
我和吉米・史密森在这玩飞盘
and me and Jimmy Smithson were playing frisbee in the bar.
我把爸爸最爱的啤酒标志弄坏了
And I broke dad's favorite beer sign?
钟旁边有霓虹灯的那个吗
The neon one with the clock?
对  爸大发脾气
Yeah, and dad went ballistic.
我第一次见到有人真会气得脸色发青
You know, I-I'd never seen somebody actually turn purple.
所以我跑回房间  开始收拾行李
So I ran up to my room, started packing a bag.
打算离家出走
You know, figuring I was gonna run away.
但你告诉他是你干的
And you told him you did it,
即使他把你摔在地上
even though he grounded you
不让你去阿迪朗达克山[位于纽约州]露营
and wouldn't let you go on that camping trip to the Adirondacks.
- 德克  - 听我说完
- Dec-- - No.
你是我见过的最善良正直的人
You are the most stand-up guy I know.
我见过你一次又一次地
I've seen you take the heat for other people
帮别人顶黑锅
over and over again,
但你这次失去的
but you got a lot more to lose here
可不仅仅是山上数日的风光
than a couple of days in the mountains.
我不在乎你在保护谁  为何要这样
And I-I don't care who you're protecting or why.
但从现在开始  由我来保护你
But as of now, I'm gonna start protecting you.
单一麦芽威士忌
Single malt.
纯的
Neat.
就来
Coming up.
帮你照看酒吧的那漂亮女孩去哪了
Where's that pretty girl who tends bar?
阿曼达吗
Amanda, is it?
我们店季节性很大
Our business is seasonal.
夏天结束后  员工就去找新工作了
When the summer ends, people move on to the next gig.
每年都如此
Happens every year.
你俩曾交往过  对吗
You two were dating, right?
你问得太多了
You ask a lot of questions.
本杰明・布鲁克斯
Benjamin Brooks.
我是丹尼尔・格雷森的代理律师
I represent Daniel Drayson.
我还有个问题
I have another question for you.
周六晚上你在哪里
Where were you Saturday night?
我准备起航去海地
I was starting to sail to Haiti.
去帮助那儿的房屋重建
I was getting ready to help with the rebuilding there.
你太舍己为人了  何事让你耽搁了
Aren't you the altruist? What stopped you?
引擎故障
Engine trouble.
真可惜
That's a shame.
秋天快到了  再要去路途可就艰辛了
Pretty soon, fall will be here. It'll be too rough a trip.
你该抓住机会离开的
Should've left when you had the chance.
有阿曼达消息的话通知我
Let me know if you hear from Amanda.
我能帮你修好船让你傍晚离开
Oh, I can have your boat fixed and ready to go by nightfall.
逃避并不能解决问题
Running away is not gonna solve anything.
我得在格雷森之前找到她
And I gotta find Amanda before the Graysons do.
你打算怎么找
And how are you gonna do that?
还不知道
I don't know yet.
客户有罪对你来说重要吗
Does it matter to you if your clients are guilty?
我从不过问
I never ask.
好冷漠无情
Cynical.
我最不想的
The last thing I need
就是使我的判断受到影响
is to have my judgment clouded.
过去20年来  我一个案子都没输过
And in 20 years, I haven't lost a case,
所以如果这记录不被打破的话
so if ain't broke...
你对此案的看法是什么
What's your take on all this?
我觉得是丹尼尔杀死了泰勒
I think Daniel shot Tyler.
而且他能成功脱罪
And I think he's gonna get away with it.
而你还继续为格雷森家工作
And yet you continue to work for the Graysons.
我来自一个叫克里登的小镇
I come from a town called Croydon,
就在伦敦的边上
just outside of London.
由于无人关心  人口越来越少
Population--no one cares and dropping.
我想要的不仅仅是策划派对
I want more out of life than planning parties
或为别人打理日常琐事
and making sure other people's lives run smoothly,
可眼下
But for now...
这就是我的工作
It's my job.
你会很上镜的
The camera sure loves you.
你这步棋若走对了
You play your cards right,
就可以借着丹尼尔的审判大展宏图
you can parlay Daniel's trial into a whole new career.
不过话说回来
But then...
我想你已经明白这一点了
I think you already know that.
你好像需要有人相伴
Looks like you could use some company.
两个月前
Two months ago,
我们被《时代》评为完美夫妇
we were being heralded in "The Times." as a golden couple,
再看看现在
and now look at us.
一个孩子因为谋杀被逮捕
One child arrested for murder,
另一个则用鄙视的目光看着我们
and the other can't look at us without contempt,
我俩离了婚却还住在同一屋檐下
Divorced but living under the same roof.
至少这屋檐下有两万平方英尺
At least it's a 20,000-square-foot roof.
我们不至于相互绊倒对方
It's not like we'll be tripping over each other.
是两万四平方英尺
24,000.
我们怎么会落到如此地步
Oh. How the hell did we get here?
我也不知道
Mm. I don't know.
我想这就是所谓的多米诺效应
I believe it's called the domino effect.
一件事牵扯到另一件事
You know, one move begets another,
于是在你还未觉察之前
and then before you know it...
它们全倒下了
they all fall down.
我很担心
I'm worried.
监狱不是丹尼尔这种人能待的
Jail is no place for a boy like Daniel.
在这个世上
There is a perception
很多人有这样一种观念
in this part of the world
认为钱权能使鬼推磨
that power and money exert undue influence.
但我明确地告诉你们
I want it clear--
在我的法庭上
in my courtroom,
正义无价  法不阿贵
justice has no price tag.
我仔细审查了大量显示丹尼尔・格雷森
I have carefully examined the wealth of forensic evidence
与犯罪现场有关的法医证据
linking Daniel Grayson to the crime scene
同时考虑到格雷森家族
and taken into consideration the Grayson family's
用之不尽的资源
unlimited resources
例如私人飞机之类
as well as private planes.
加之此案的严重性
Given the serious nature of this crime,
我在此驳回丹尼尔・格雷森的
I hereby deny bail...
-我的天  -保释请求
- Oh , my God - for Daniel Grayson...
在等待审判期间  他将被押送至
And order him to be remanded to the maximum security
赖克斯岛最高安全级别的看守所
correctional facility on Rikers Island while he awaits trial.
丹尼尔  丹尼尔
Daniel. Daniel.
法警  请将被告人带走
Bailiff, would you please remove the defendant?
你们得做点什么
You gotta do something.
格雷森家是否将法官的裁决
Do the Graysons see the judge's ruling
视作一个巨大的挫败
as a huge defeat?
格雷森家族非常尊重
The Grayson family have the greatest respect
法庭关于拒绝保释丹尼尔的决定
for the court's decision regarding Daniel's bail.
但他们的确认为这是一个小挫折
But they do view this as a minor setback,
他们确信司法机关将会尽快纠正
and one they're sure the justice system will remedy
这个错误的
as quickly as possible.
我同时希望
I'd also like--
你哪儿也不会去了吧
You're not going anywhere, are you?
不  德克兰需要我
No, Declan needs me.
为家着想  值得赞扬啊
Oh, kudos for the family values.
可你这是犯了弥天大错
But you're making a colossal mistake.
你是不想要喝酒了吗
Does this mean you don't want a drink?
来两杯吧
Make it a double.
这个秋天长着呢
It's gonna be a long fall.
诺氏企业  技术部门
Nolcorp, I.T. Department,
我是诺兰
Hey, it's Nolan.
那些我们帮忙从网上撤下来的格雷森家的照片
Those photos we pulled down for the Graysons,
我要你找到这些照片的源头
I need you to find out where they originated.
逆境下会诞生意想不到的同盟
Adversity creates unexpected alliances...
但此时缔结的条约
But treaties of this nature
极少是平等公正的
seldom form with an equality of power.
这位不是
Well, here she is--
媒体的新宠儿吗
The media's new it girl.
对女王最爱的劳工来说
Mm. It's quite an upgrade
实在是一大飞跃啊
from the queen's favorite worker bee.
我想你叫我来不是要签名的吧
I take it you didn't summon me here for an autograph.
我很支持一举成名  阿什
I'm all for a meteoric rise, Ash,
不过  我跟着直觉
But, uh, I followed a hunch,
找到了轰动网络的
and sourced the scandal pics
丑闻照片的来源
that are blowing up the internet.
猜猜最后源头是在哪儿
And guess where the trail ends.
还有谁知道这事
Who else knows?
就我们俩
Just us...
暂时如此
For now.
从恐惧与不信任中建立起的忠诚
Loyalties forged in apprehension and mistrust...
薄如蝉翼
are tenuous at best...
在对抗无情的真相之光时
Easily broken when held up
就会轻易崩溃
to the unforgiving light of the truth.
但在最为绝望的黑暗之中
But in the darkness of our most desperate hours...
常常是这样的忠诚给予我们力量
It's often these loyalties that lend us the strength
完成必须要做的事
to do what we know must be done.
48小时前
你应该听从我警告的
You should've heeded my warning.
你都干了什么
What did you do?
是你缺少自我约束  才导致了这些混乱
海滩边到底发生了什么
What happened on the beach?
那个男的正要揭露你
The boy was going to expose you.
你逃不掉的  泰勒
You won't get away with this, Tyler.
我当然逃得掉
Sure I will,
可艾米莉就不会了
but Emily won't.
不
No!
别过来
Stay back!
也许你该先给艾米莉打个电话
Maybe you should call Emily first.
问她同不同意你扣动扳机
Ask her permission to pull the trigger.
她就是只披着羊皮的狼  你个蠢货
She's a wolf in sheep's clothing, you idiot.
而你就是只无助的小绵羊
And you're just a helpless little lamb
一步一步走向屠场
headed for the slaughter.
求求你  救救我
Please. Help me.
不要
No!
可那里还有别人
But there were others.
你叫她阿曼达的那个女孩
The girl you call Amanda.
她已经被妥善处理了
She has been taken care of.
阿曼达
Amanda!
然后
And then...
杰克
Jack.
另外那个你有好感的男孩
The other boy you have feelings for.
你可没法两个都救
You cannot save them both.
一颗充满疑问和困惑的矛盾之心
A conflicted heart feeds on doubt and confusion.
会让你怀疑你所选择的道路
It will make you question your path...
你的策略
Your tactics...
你的动机
Your motives.
当你举目远望  却只看到一片黑暗时
When you stare ahead and darkness is all you see,
只有理智和决心
only reason and determination
能将你拉出深渊
can pull you back from the abyss.